viralstyle.com 2018-11-25

# Viralstyle

We at Viral Style, LLC., ("Viral Style", "Viralstyle", "we", "us" or "our") know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously.  This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you use or otherwise engage with our  websites and software sites (collectively, the "Site"). It describes what types of personally identifiable information we collect, how we use that information, and who we share that  information with. Certain terms that are capitalized but not defined in this policy will have the meaning given to them in our Terms of Use.

If you are based in Europe for the purposes of European data protection legislation, the controller of your personal information  is Viral Style, LLC with offices at 601 North Ashley Drive, Suite 500, Tampa, FL 33602.

By using or accessing the Site in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy  Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information as set forth below.

## The Personal Information We Collect

 **Information You Provide to Us:**  
We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, if you register to sell, we’ll record the registration information that you provided.  Also, when you purchase a product, we will collect shipping and payment related information. Certain information may be required to register with us, purchase or to  take advantage of some of our features. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information,  personal description. If you do not provide us with such information, your access to or use of the Site may be limited.

 **Other Information Collected from Your Use of the Site:**  
Whenever you interact with our Site, we may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser or device,  which may include your IP address, device identification, "cookie" information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our Site,  and the page or feature you requested. The data that we collect can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Site, and we can use that  knowledge to make the Site better and more useful to as many users as possible. We do not track information about your online activity after you leave our Sites.

 **Cookies**  
"Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages and features  in our Site are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device’s acceptance  of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features. For more information review our Cookie Policy <https://viralstyle.com/privacy/cookies> .

 **Information Collected from Third Parties:**  
We may collect Personal Information from third parties we reasonably believe have the right to provide such information to us  (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery sites, advertising networks, analytics  providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies). In addition, we may collect Personal Information with your consent or as required by law or regulation.

## How We Use Personal Information

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Sitec  (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud;
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or sites.

 **Viralstyle may also use your Personal Information as follows:**

  * To operate and maintain the Site (such as, for the purposes of fixing malfunctions, testing our security systems, etc.).
  * To provide you with the features, functions and benefits of the Site.
  * To process orders or subscriptions (i.e. charging your credit card).
  * Communicate with sellers, depending on communication settings.
  * To enhance, improve and further develop the Site (such as, creating new features or functions, refining the user experience, increasing Site technical performance, etc.).
  * We will use your contact information to provide you with notices related to your use of the Site.
  * Where we have your permission to do so, or where you are an existing customer and we have a legitimate business interest (see below) and have carried out a  balancing test to determine that your rights do not outweigh that legitimate interest, we will use your contact information (such as, your email address)  to provide you with promotional and marketing emails. You can opt-out of receiving promotional and marketing emails at any time, but if you do you may not  receive the full benefit of the Site. Opting-out can be done by following the instructions at the bottom of the promotional material or by contacting us  using the information under "Contacting Us" section below.
  * To help personalize the Site experience for you (such as, remembering your information so you will not have to enter it each time you use the Site).
  * And for the other purposes referenced in the "Who Viralstyle Shares Your Personal Information With" section below (such as, for the purposes of legal compliance).

 **Legitimate Interests**  
We process Personal Information for certain legitimate business purposes, which include some or all of the following:

  * where the processing enables us to enhance, modify, personalize or otherwise improve our sites' communications for the benefit of our customers;
  * processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with order confirmations and order status updates;
  * to identify and prevent fraud;
  * to enhance the security of our network and information systems;
  * to better understand how people interact with our websites;
  * to provide postal communications which we think will be of interest to you e.g. information about new products and sites; about new initiatives; case studies and  whitepapers; to determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising.

"Legitimate Interests" means the interests of our company in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best site/products/service and the best and most secure experience.

When we process your Personal Information for our legitimate interests, we make sure to consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative),  and your rights under data protection laws. Our legitimate business interests do not automatically override your interests - we will not use your Personal Information  for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).

You can object to our use of your Personal Information for our legitimate interests. See the "Your Rights" section below.

## Who Viralstyle Shares Your Personal Information With

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. However, we may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this section:

 **With your Consent:**  
We may share your personal information with third parties with your express consent, other than the cases below.

 **Agents:**  
We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or sites to you;  for example, we may use a payment processing site to charge your Card. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal  Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

 **Business Transfers:**  
We may choose to buy or sell the assets of Viral Style, LLC. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets  that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control,  Personal Information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

 **Protection of Viralstyle and Others:**  
We may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our Terms  and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Viralstyle, our employees, our users, or others.

 **Aggregated Personal Information that’s no longer personally identifiable:**  
We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you are not individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate  usage information to our partners, who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Sites, so that they, too, can provide you  with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate information to any third party in a manner that would identify you personally, as an individual.

 **How Long We Keep Your Information For:**  
We will retain personal information for as long as it is needed for legitimate business purposes to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes  of satisfying any legal, accounting, tax, fulfillment, or reporting requirements.  To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information,  the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether  we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

## What You can do to Your Personal Information

 **Deleting your account:**  
You can delete your account by emailing support@viralstyle.com. Subject to the Exceptions below, when you request for us to delete your account for the Site, your  data will be permanently deleted from our servers and access to your account will be disabled.

 **Exceptions:**  
We may retain your Personal Information in accordance with our retention policy (see the "How Long We Keep Your Information For" section) and to the extent required  to comply with (or we deem it reasonable in light of) any laws or regulations.

 **For those in the European Union, the United Kingdom or Switzerland:**  
If you are based in the European Union you can also do the following:

 **Ask us to stop contacting you with direct marketing.**  
Even if you have accepted the processing of your personal information for marketing purposes, you have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal  information for such purposes. Let us know what method of contact you are not happy with if you are unhappy with certain ways of contacting you only  (for example, you may be happy for us to contact you by email but not by telephone).

 **Requesting a copy of your information.**  
You can request a copy of your information which we hold (in Europe this is known as a subject access request). If you would like a copy of some or all of it,  please contact us and let us know the information you want a copy of, including any account or reference numbers, if you have them. Any subject access request may  be subject to a reasonable fee to cover the cost of providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

 **Correcting any mistakes in your information.**  
You can require us to correct any mistakes in your information which we hold free of charge. If you would like to do this, please contact us and let us know the information  that is incorrect and the information you want it replaced with.

 **Request us to cease processing your information.**  
You may request that we cease processing your personal information. If you make such a request, we shall retain only the amount of personal information pertaining  you that is necessary to ensure that no further processing of your personal information takes place.

## Data Portability Request

You have rights to obtain a copy of some of the Personal Information that we hold on you and reuse or share it for your own purposes ("right to data portability").

The right to data portability only applies:

  * to Personal Information you’ve provided to us (i.e. not any other information),
  * where we are processing your Personal Information because you have provided your consent for us to do so, or under a contract with you; and
  * when processing is carried out by automated means.

We can refuse your data portability request if the processing does not satisfy the above criteria. Also, if the Personal Information concerns more than one individual,  we may not be able to transfer the information to you if doing so would prejudice the other person’s rights.

## The Location of Your Personal Information

While your Personal Information is in our possession, it will be primarily stored at hosting facilities located in the USA. These facilities are either operated by Viralstyle  or our third-party providers. By using the Site you are consenting to have your Personal Information stored, transferred and processed in the USA.

## The Security of Your Personal Information

Viralstyle takes certain precautions to protect your Personal Information and to limit the risk that it will be accessed without authorization, including use of certain industry  standard technologies and practices. That said, we cannot guarantee the security of such information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors,  may compromise the security of user information at any time. No security system is perfect, so your use of the Site is at your own risk.

If we learn of a security systems breach, which is likely to result in a high risk to you directly then we may attempt to notify you via email, phone, physical mail, or by a  posting on your Site account page so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Pursuant to our Terms you have consented to receive such notice by electronic means  (provided that such consent is void where prohibited by applicable law). To receive a free written notice of a security breach, or if you have any questions about the security  of the Site, please contact us at support@viralstyle.com.

In addition to the security measures referenced above, your Site account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your  account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have  finished accessing your account.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last changed on the date set forth at the bottom of the policy. We’re constantly trying to improve the Site, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy  from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by editing the date at the top of this policy, by sending you an email, and/or by some other means. Please note that  if you’ve opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Site, and  you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Site after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes.  Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

## Information from Children

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16. If you are under 16, please do not attempt to register for the Site or send any personal  information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you believe that a child under 16 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at support@viralstyle.com

## Complaints

You may direct any inquiries or complaints concerning this Privacy Policy to us using the information under the "Contacting Us" section below. We will respond within 45 days.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message at support@viralstyle.com, or: 601 North Ashley Drive, Suite 500, Tampa, FL 33602.

## Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over  other websites and their content. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such  sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Contact Information:

Email: [{{privacy.config.emailSupport}}](mailto:%7B%7Bprivacy.config.emailSupport%7D%7D)  
Telephone: [{{privacy.config.phone}}](tel:{{privacy.config.phone}})

 _Updated 5/24/2018_
